PATTI PERLOCK

WEB DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

Teacher's Assistant - Web Development | Brainstation

FEB 2021 - APR 2021, REMOTE

- Selected to be one of three teacher's assistants from a cohort of 30 students based on academic achievement and proven ability to mentor others.
- Mentoring students by leading labs, question and answer periods and engaging with them through Slack.
- Presenting live code-along solutions for morning challenges.
- Marking assignments and delivering comments for code improvements.

Senior Database Administrator | Kirkland Lake Gold

JAN 2017 - DEC 2020, TIMMINS, ON, CA

- Spearheaded the development and execution of a SQL server database remotely within 3 months, allowing a major exploration drilling program to commence according to schedule.
- Delivered streamlined reporting and automated tracking tools to senior level management, summarizing production metrics.
- Collaborated with end users and software developers remotely to ensure functionality requirements were met while simultaneously providing training and support.
- Designed and regulated a detailed QAQC monitoring program that reports the precision and accuracy of assay data, improving data reliability.

EDUCATION

BrainStation | Diploma Candidate, Web Development

NOV 2020 - FEB 2021, TORONTO, ON

University of Western Ontario | Masters in Geophysics

SEPT 2005 - 2010, LONDON, ON, CA

CSEG Scholarship, **Thesis:** Imaging Faults in 3D Using the Pattern Informatics Technique

University of Western Ontario | Bachelors in Geophysics

SEPT 2000 - 2005, LONDON, ON, CA

Honour Role, **Thesis:** Modeling of the July 1998 Northridge Aftershock Using a Linear Inversion and Genetic Algorithm

PROJECTS

Plan2Train | Lead Coder, UI/UX Developer | Visit

FEB 2021 - BRAINSTATION CAPSTONE PROJECT

An organizational app focused on helping small businesses in the personal training space. MERN (MongoDB, Express, React, Node), Passport, Heroku, APIs, Cloud Storage.

pattiperlock@gmail.com 705-262-8679 linkedin.com/in/pattiperlock github.com/pperlock www.pattiperlock.com

PROFILE

Dedicated to tackling problems from start to finish while focusing on efficiency and user experience.

My strong background in geophysics and computer programming provides a solid foundation in logical reasoning, algorithm development and innovative thinking.

My goal is to be part of a team where I can continue to learn and employ my passion for problem solving, bringing ideas to life through imagination and code.

SKILLS

Front-End: HTML5, CSS, SASS, Javascript, React, Document Object Model (DOM), APIs

BackEnd: Node.js, Express.js, Web APIs, User Authentication

Database: MySQL, MongoDB

Deployment and Development: Heroku, GitHub, WebPack

Other: VBA, MATLAB, Excel, Access, Perl, Datamine Fusion Suite (DBMS)